weddinginspirasi.com 2019-07-02

# Privacy Policy for Wedding Inspirasi | Wedding Inspirasi

Updated on May 24, 2018

WeddingInspirasi.com (Wedding Inspirasi, this Website, our Website) collects **Personally Identifiable Information**  and **Non-Personally Identifiable Information** **.**

**Important:  **WHEN YOU ACCESS OUR WEBSITE, YOU AGREE TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY AND [TERMS OF SERVICE](http://www.weddinginspirasi.com/terms-of-service/ "Terms of Service"). IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY OR TERMS OF SERVICE, OR TO ANY CHANGES WE MAY SUBSEQUENTLY MAKE, PLEASE STOP ACCESSING OUR WEBSITE.

Personally and Non-Personally Identifiable Information may be collected automatically when using this website, and when using, but not limited to, the following services associated with this Website:

**Advertisements and Advertising Networks _  
_** Google Adsense  
BrideClick Network (Glam, Inc)  
DoubleClick for Publisher

**__****Traffic Measurement _  
_** Google Analytics  
Statcounter

**__****Interaction with External Social Networks and Platforms  
**For example, when you use the share button and social widgets for Pinterest, Facebook, Instagram, Twitter, Tumblr, Google+, Gmail, LinkedIn and others

**Content Commenting and Subscription to Services Provided by This Website**

**Other Technologies  
**For example, Web Beacons and Tracking URLS

## Types of Information We Collect

Wedding Inspirasi collects two kinds of information:

  1. ****Non-Personally Identifiable Information**** (or Anonymous Data) which is automatically collected when you visit this Website or that you provide;
  2. **Personally Identifiable Information** (or Personal Data), or information that you provide that personally identifies you.

## How We Collect Information

There are two ways that Information may be collected:

  1. **Automatically collected;**
  2. **Provided by you.**

**Information that are automatically collected.**  
When you visit WeddingInspirasi.com, the Website automatically receives and stores information including **IP address** , **web pages viewed** , **date and time** , and **responses to advertisements** delivered by our various advertising partners. This information is collected by us or through the use of third party services such as Google Analytics and Statcounter. We may collect data from the device you are using including location data, device type, the operating system you are using, device settings, unique device identifiers, and crash data. The amount of data available to be collected is dependent on the settings that you may set on your device. More information on Device Data that may be collected

**Information provided by you.**  
Wedding Inspirasi (and the third parties with whom we work with) may collect and maintain information that _you have provided to us_ during your visit to WeddingInspirasi.com and our social media channels. For example, when you register to receive website updates, RSS feed, comments on feed, or new post notifications, you might supply us with personally identifiable information such as your **email address**. This website also lets you share information with other people. You have control over how you share Personal Data. For example, you can share an image on Pinterest or Instagram publicly or on a secret board or private account. Remember, when you share information publicly, your content may become accessible through search engines.

You also may give us permission to access your information in other services. For example, you may be able to link your Facebook account to the Website, which allows us to obtain information from those accounts (like your friends or contacts). The information we get from those services depends on your settings or their privacy policies, so be sure to check what those are.

**Before You Provide Personal Information Online…  
**Acknowledge that you:

  1. can choose not to receive communications from us or third parties vendors by e-mail or social media;
  2. can elect not to leave comments or share information using your personal information or personal social media account;
  3. can choose not to share personal information publicly;
  4. will be careful to maintain the secrecy of your passwords and/or account information and be responsible about protecting your personal information and identity whenever you are online;
  5. will review the privacy policies of each website and service used before deciding to share personal information;
  6. will review the privacy settings of your devices to choose the privacy settings that are right for you.

**Links to Third-Party Sites.** This Website contains links to third-party sites, which are maintained by third parties. Please be aware that Wedding Inspirasi is not responsible for and cannot control the privacy policies of these other linked sites or their practices. We encourage you to  note when you leave our Website and read the privacy policies on these sites for applicable privacy practices relating to personally identifiable information you may choose to provide in interacting with these websites and the non-personally identifiable information collected through the use of cookies and other technologies collected via those sites because they **may differ** from our privacy practices.

**This Website is Not Intended for Children.** We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from Children. We ask that minors (under the age of 18) only use this Website in conjunction with your parents or guardians. If you learn that your minor child has provided us with personal information without your consent, please contact us.

## Wedding Inspirasi uses “Cookies”

This Website use “cookies” to collect or log certain information. A cookie is a small data file that a website stores on a personal computer and which it can later retrieve. An example of how this Website may use cookies is to store your preferences or serve advertisements tailored to your preferences.

Third parties may also use their own cookies to serve ads and personalize content. Wedding Inspirasi does not control these cookies or the data collection practices of these third parties. You are responsible for any third-party Personal Data obtained, published or shared through this Website and confirm that you have the third party’s consent to provide the Data to the us.

We do not sell your personally identifiable information to third parties or disclose your personally identifiable information to unaffiliated third parties, however please note the third parties have their own privacy practices, and may sell your personally identifiable or non-personally identifiable information that they may obtain from this Website for any reason (e.g. when you enter a sweepstakes run on this website). You declare to be aware of that the privacy policies of third parties **may differ** from this Website’s privacy policy. For more information about these companies’ separate privacy policies, practices, and use of cookies, you should refer to the third parties directly. Some are linked below:

BrideClick and Glam, Inc.  
<http://www.brideclick.net/privacy-policy/>[  
](http://www.brideclick.net/privacy-policy/)<https://www.glam.com/privacy-policy/>

Google  
<https://policies.google.com/privacy/update>

**Disabling Cookies**  
Your browser may allow you to set how it handles cookies, such as declining all cookies or prompting you to decide whether to accept each cookie. But please note that some parts of the Websites or Services that are dependent on cookies, may not work as intended or may not work at all without cookies.

If you use more than one type of browser, or more than one computer or mobile device to access the Internet, you will need to opt out in each browser and on each device that you use.

## How We Use and Share the Information Collected

**Personally Identifiable Information  
**The personally information you submit to us is generally used to carry out your requests, respond to your inquiries or in other ways associated with the circumstances in which you provide the information. We may also use this information to later contact you for a variety of reasons, such as customer service, providing you with promotional information for our service or our advertisers, or to communicate with you about content or other information you have posted or shared with us via our Website. You may opt-out from receiving future promotional information from us, or instruct that we not share your information with third parties, as outlined below.

In certain instances we may also share your personally identifiable information with third-parties performing functions on our behalf. Examples include third parties that administer our promotions, provide us with marketing or promotional assistance, analyze our data, and assist us with customer service. These third parties agree to use this information, and we share this information with them, only to carry out our requests. In addition, we may share your personally identifiable information with participating sponsors to a program or promotion you enter via our Website, for example when you enter a sweepstakes or contest, and with third parties who assist us in using the content or other information you have posted or shared with us via our Website. Further, we may share your personally identifiable information with third parties such as our co-promotional partners and others with whom we have marketing or other relationships. Except as provided in this Privacy Policy, our Terms of Use, or outlined when you submit the information, your personally identifiable information will not be shared or sold to any third parties without your prior approval. Please note, however, that the third parties may sell your personally identifiable or non-personally identifiable information that they may obtain through this Website for any reason. You declare to be aware of this.

**Non-Personally Identifiable Information**  
We use non-personal information in a variety of ways, including to help analyze site traffic, understand user needs and trends, carry out targeted promotional activities and to improve our services. We may use your non-personal information by itself or aggregate it with information we have obtained from others. We may share your non-personal information with our affiliated companies and third parties to achieve these objectives and others. Remember, aggregate information is anonymous information that does not personally identify you. Website usage information may be collected using various methods, such as the following:

  1. Cookies
  2. Web beacons and URL trackers
  3. Device identifiers
  4. Embedded scripts

**We may also disclose your anonymous and personal information to third parties:**

  1. In the event that we sell or buy any business or assets, in which case we may disclose your personal data to the prospective seller or buyer of such business or assets.
  2. If all or substantially all of our assets are acquired by a third party, in which case personal data held by us about our customers will be one of the transferred assets.
  3. As permitted or required by law, such as in connection with a legal process. Your Personal Data may be used for legal purposes by the Owner in Court or in the stages leading to possible legal action arising from improper use of this Website or the related Services. You declare to be aware that the Owner may be required to reveal personal data upon request of public authorities.

## How Long We Keep Your Information

**Personally Identifiable Information  
**Personal Data shall be processed and stored for as long as required by the purpose they have been collected for. For example, if you subscribed to our Newsletter, your Personal Data may be kept until you opt out. As long as consent is not withdrawn, we may also hold on to your Personal Data for a longer period than required by the purpose they have been collected for. This may be for the purpose of reports, audits, legal obligations or upon the order of an authority. Personal Data retention from third party service depends on your settings with their service.

**Non-Personally Identifiable Information  
**Wedding Inspirasi is required to retain certain Anonymous Data collected from you in order to provide audited information to advertisers and auditors. As a result, ad reporting and delivery data is retained for as long as is necessary for these purposes. Some of the data may be aggregated for statistical purposes and retained indefinitely.

## Contact and Opt-Out Information

You may contact us as at support@weddinginspirasi.com if:

  1. you have questions or comments about this Privacy Policy;
  2. you wish to amend any personally identifiable information you have provided;
  3. you want to opt-out from receiving future correspondence, including emails from us or
  4. you wish to withdraw your consent to sharing your personally identifiable information with others. We will respond to your request and, if applicable and appropriate, make the requested change in our active databases as soon as reasonably practicable.

Opting out will not remove advertisements on this Website.

## Changes to this Privacy Policy

Wedding Inspirasi reserves the right to make changes to this privacy policy at any time. You will be notified of the change on this page, or by posting a notice on our Website prior to the change becoming effective. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our cookie practices. Your continued use of our Websites constitutes your agreement to be bound by such changes to this Policy. If you do not accept the terms of this Policy, you can discontinue use of our Website, or disable cookies.

## Limitation of Liability

In using WeddingInspirasi.com, the user agrees that the OWNERS shall not be liable for any damage, loss or injury directly or indirectly resulting from the use of this website. While we strive to protect your personally identifiable information and privacy, we cannot guarantee or warrant the security of any information you disclose or transmit to us online and are not responsible for the theft, destruction or inadvertent disclosure of your personally identifiable information. In the event that your “personally identifiable information” (as the term or similar terms are defined by any applicable law requiring notice upon a security breach) is compromised, we may notify you by email (in our sole and absolute discretion) to the last email address you have provided to us in the most expedient time reasonable under the circumstances; provided, however, delays in notification may occur while we take necessary measures to determine the scope of the breach and restore reasonable integrity to the system, as well as for the legitimate needs of law enforcement if notification would impede a criminal investigation.

## Contact information

**Owner and Data Controller (Owner)  
**Wedding Inspirasi

**Owner contact email:**  [info@weddinginspirasi.com](mailto:info@weddinginspirasi.com)

**Device Data**  
Device attributes: information such as the operating system, hardware and software versions, battery level, signal strength, available storage space, browser type, app and file names and types, and plugins | Device operations: information about operations and behaviors performed on the device, such as whether a window is foregrounded or backgrounded, or mouse movements (which can help distinguish humans from bots)| Identifiers: unique identifiers, device IDs, and other identifiers, such as from games, apps or accounts you use, and Family Device IDs | Device signals: Bluetooth signals, and information about nearby Wi-Fi access points, beacons, and cell towers | Data from device settings: information you allow us to receive through device settings you turn on, such as access to your GPS location, camera or photos | Network and connections: information such as the name of your mobile operator or ISP, language, time zone, mobile phone number, IP address, connection speed and, in some cases, information about other devices that are nearby or on your network | Cookie data: data from cookies stored on your device, including cookie IDs and settings.
